phpmyrealty.com 2014-07-01

# phpMyRealty.com - Privacy Policy - php/SQL Real Estate Classifieds Directory, php Real Estate Listings Directory, Realtors / Agents Directory Script

**Testimonials**  

I really appreciated the way PHPmyrealty.com support department worked with me to get my site online and functioning the way I needed it to. My previous experience was only with the Front Page format, and the support department guided me through making the required changed I needed on the php files and working with the modular components.

\- REII Assets

| 

### Privacy Policy

We respect your privacy, and we want you to feel comfortable using the web site herein. 

phpMyRealty.com's legal parent entity, Next Click Ventures, LLC does collect certain personally identifiable information that may be used to provide you with customized services, content, networking opportunities, industry information and/or advertisements. Personally identifiable information is collected when you register to receive certain Next Click Ventures, LLC services, products or offers. Next Click Ventures, LLC may also request personally identifiable information when the user elects to participate in other Next Click Ventures, LLC affiliated or sponsored programs, including, but not limited to, sweepstakes, contests, and/or other such promotions. 

The Next Click Ventures, LLC site provides users the opportunity to opt out of receiving communications from us. Users may unsubscribe from our email newsletter if they wish to no longer receive communications. You may unsubscribe from newsletter mailings at anytime by following the directions on the bottom of the e-mail sent to you or by contacting us directly for help. 

Next Click Ventures, LLC may share the collected personally identifiable information with a sponsor or other third party that may be interested in serving you. Next Click Ventures, LLC will request and verify your consent before any personally identifiable information is provided to sponsors or third parties. You may also inform Next Click Ventures, LLC at any time not to share your personally identifiable information with third parties by sending an e-mail message to us using the contact page and requesting that your personally identifiable information not be released to third parties. 

Next Click Ventures, LLC may use your personally identifiable information to provide you with any of our present and future services. We may also use this information to notify you or contact you with regard to any problem with, or the expiration of such services. For this reason, Next Click Ventures, LLC may find it necessary to disclose your personally identifiable information to one or more Next Click Ventures, LLC agents and/or contractors and their subcontractors, but such agents, contractors, and subcontractors will be required to agree to use any personally identifiable information obtained from Next Click Ventures, LLC for only such purposes. 

Personally identifiable information also may be disclosed to the proper authorities in special situations where Next Click Ventures, LLC has reason to believe that doing so is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against anyone damaging, injuring, or interfering (intentionally or unintentionally) with Next Click Ventures, LLC's rights, property, users, or anyone else who may be harmed by such activities. Next Click Ventures, LLC may reveal personally identifiable information when we have been informed by law enforcement authorities or have established a good faith belief that the law requires Next Click Ventures, LLC to do so. 

We reserve the right to change our privacy policy at any time by posting revisions on the Next Click Ventures, LLC web site. This privacy policy is not intended to, and does not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.
